#Random Encounter

##Objectives:

* Build a message generator program. 
* Every time a user runs the program, they get a randomized encounter.
* The program will generates three parts of the encounter: setting, obstacle, and attitude.

##Project Tasks:
* Plan your project 
* Come up with your topic
* Create script and run it locally
* Set up version control
* Store Message Components
* Create the message
* Put the program together
* Next Steps

##Project Timeline:
* Write Readme outlining project and objectives
* Create gitHub repository
* Comment .js file for functions within program
* Create random number generator die roller
* Create objects containing strings for random phrases
* Create function to combine random strings together for encounter
* Return encounter description

